Ennai Pol Oruvan is a romance film directed by A. C. Tirulokchandar.
Rajasekar / Sekar / Sundaramoorthy, played by Sivaji Ganesan.
Lakshmi, played by Sharada.
Usha, played by Usha Nandhini.
Sundaramoorthy's father, played by Chittoor V. Nagayya.
Sabapathy, played by R. S. Manohar.
Namachivayam, played by M. R. R. Vasu.
Ennai Pol Oruvan (transl.
A Man Like Me) is a 1978 Indian Tamil-language action drama film directed by T.
Ramanna and written by Sakthi T.
Krishnasamy.
A remake of Uttam Kumar starrer Bengali film Tasher Ghar (1957), the film stars
Sivaji Ganesan in dual roles, alongside Saratha, Ushanandini and Aalam.
It was released on 18 March 1978, and performed above average at the box office.
The tone is emotional.